Those three think they can mock me? Screw that!
!يستخف بي أولئك الثلاثة، سحقًا لذلك
I'm considering this a formal declaration of war.
سأعدّ هذا إعلانًا للحرب ضدي
Perfect timing, Mohji!
!أتيت إذًا يا موجي
Mind if I go after Roronoa Zoro?
أتمانع أخذي رأس رورونوا زورو؟
Be my guest.
كلّا
What's with that dog?
ما بالُ هذا الكلب؟
A dog!
!كلب
Hey, Zoro! It's not moving at all!
إنه لا يتحرك إطلاقًا يا زورو
Hell if I care! It can do whatever it wants!
لا يهمني، يمكنه فعل ما يشاء
Think it's dead?
أهو ميّت يا ترى؟
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow! Yee-ow!
!مؤلم! مؤلم! مؤلم
Ow, ow, ow! What's the big deal, you stupid dog?!
!مؤلم حقًّا! ماذا تفعل أيها الكلب الغبي؟ اتركني
Would you stop messing around at a time like this?!
!أتستوعب وضعنا الحالي؟
Stupid dog...
...كلب لعين
Not enough blood...
...أفتقر للدم
Hey, Navigator!
مرحبًا أيتها الملاحة
I guess you can have this since you saved me!
سأعطيك هذا بما أنك أنقذتني
You went and got it for me?!
أكلَّفتِ نفسكِ بجلبه من أجلي؟
Now we're even.
لا تسِئ فهمي
I'm saved!
أنقذتِني
You stupid, stupid dog! Stupid dog!
!أيها الكلب الأحمق اللعين
That's not food! Gimme back that key!
!هذا ليس طعامًا! أخرجه! أخرج المفتاح! أخرجه
Gimme! Gimme! Gimme!
!أخرجه! أخرجه! أخرجه
Stop that!
!ويحكم
Quit bullying Chouchou, you delinquents!
!لا تتنمروا على شوشو أيها الصغار
Chouchou?
شوشو؟
Who are you, old-timer?
من تكون أيها العجوز؟
I'm this town's mayor!
،أنا عمدة هذه البلدة
Who are you?!
!ماذا عنكم؟
Huh?
!عجبًا
How's Zoro?!
كيف حاله؟
He needs to see a doctor,
ينبغي له زيارة طبيب
but he said he'd sleep it off and went to bed.
ولكنه قال أنه سيشفى إن نام
So this dog's name is Chouchou?
يُدعى هذا الكلب شوشو إذًا؟
What's he just sitting here for?
ما الذي يفعله بالجلوس في مكانٍ كهذا؟
He's guarding the shop.
يحمي المحل
Yes. A good friend of mine owned this shop.
...أجل
There you go.
.خذ
I'm just here to feed his dog in his place.
لذا أنا هنا لإطعام كلبه نيابةً عنه
"In his place"?
نيابةً عنه؟
Yes.
...أجل
He passed away. An illness took him three months ago.
فقد توفي جراء مرضٍ قبل ثلاثة أشهر...
You mean to tell us he's been waiting here for his master all this time?
أتعني أنه ينتظر عودة صاحبه طوال هذا الوقت؟
That's the general consensus...
...هذا ما يقوله الجميع
but I don't think that's the case.
ولكنّي لا أعتقد ذلك
Chouchou is a smart dog.
،شوشو كلب ذكي
He's probably long since realized that his master has passed on.
على الأرجح أنّه يدرك أن صاحبه توفي منذ وقت طويل
Then why is he guarding the shop?
لمَ يحمي المحل إذًا؟
I believe it's because Chouchou regards this shop as his treasure.
قد يكون ذلك لكون شوشو يعدّ هذا المحل كنزًا بالنسبة له
I think he continues to protect it in memory of his loving master.
وأعتقد أنه يستمر بحمايته لأنه يعده تذكارًا من صاحبه المحب للكلاب
I've tried to get him somewhere safer on many occasions,
حاولت نزحه مرات عديدة
but he won't budge from this spot.
ولكنه يأبى الحراك من هنا
Huh? What are those roars?!
!ما هذا الزئير؟
It's him! Mohji the Beast Tamer!
!إنه مروّض الوحوش موجي
What do you mean "Beast Tamer"?!
ماذا تعني بمروّض الوحوش؟
W-Wait! Hold on!
!تـ-تمهل لحظة
C'mon, something's coming.
،هناك شيء قادم
Gimme back the key.
!أعِد لي المفتاح
Oh, I see your friends have deserted you.
،أرى أن رفقاءك هجروك
And you had only just escaped…
...مع أنك تمكنت من الهرب أخيرًا
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I am Mohji the Beast Tamer, a member of the Buggy Pirates.
أنا عضو في طاقم قراصنة باغي، مروّض الوحوش موجي
That sure is a weird animal suit you got on!
يا لها من بذلة حيوانات غريبة لترتديها
How rude! This is my hair!
!يا لوقاحتك، هذا شعري
That's even weirder!
.وهذا أغرب
Do you think you're safe just because you're in that cage?
هل أنت مسترخٍ لأنك داخل الزنزانة؟
You must not know who I am!
!لا بد أنك لا تعرف قدرتي المرعبة
There is no animal in this world that Mohji the Beast Tamer cannot tame!
!لا يوجد حيوان في هذا العالم لا يستطيع موجي مروّض الوحوش ترويضه
Shake!
صافحني
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
!مؤلم! مؤلم! مؤلم
You're just some nameless thief.
لستَ سوى لص متسلل مجهول
I couldn't care less if you live or die. Tell me where Roronoa Zoro is!
لست مهتمًا بسلب حياتك، أخبرني عن مكان رورونوا زورو
No!
أرفض
Sic him, Richie!
!عليك به يا ريتشي
Nice! The cage is open!
!مرحى، فُتحت الزنزانة
Instant death.
.موتٌ فوريّ
Good boy, Richie.
أحسنت يا ريتشي
Now, let's find Zoro. Defeating him will bolster my reputation.
لتبحث عن زورو الآن، فهزيمته ستذيع صيتي
Ah, a pet food store.
فهمت، محل أطعمة حيوانات أليفة
Fine, but eat quickly!
!كل وجبتك بسرعة
What the...?
ماذا؟
Is this mutt really trying to keep us out of this pathetic little shop?
أيعقل أن هذا الكلب يحمي هذا المحل؟
But at least I'm out of that cage.
ولكنني خرجت من الزنزانة الآن
Alright!
!حسنٌ
Now I can kick some butt and get that thief Nami to be our navigator!
!سأبرحهم ضربًا ثم سأجعل اللصة نامي تصبح ملاحتنا
How did you survive that?!
!كيف لكَ أن تكون حيًّا؟
You're alive!
!أنت حي
Something wrong with that?
ألا ينبغي عليَّ أن أكون حيًّا؟
People don't normally crash through buildings and walk away from it!
!من الغريب أن تكون حيًّا تُرزَق بعد أن قُذِفتَ مخترقًا عدَّة منازل
They don't?
حقًّا؟
Why did you come to this town in the first place?
ما غايتكَ من المجيء لهذه البلدة من الأساس؟
Why get mixed up with those pirates?
لماذا تتورطون مع أولئك القراصنة؟
I've just now decided on our goal.
،قرَّرت غايتنا توًّا
To get a map to the Grand Line and find a navigator!
!وهي أن نحصل على خريطة الغراند لاين وملَّاحة
That guy in the animal costume was looking for Zoro! I gotta find him!
قال رجل بذلة الحيوان إنَّه يبحث عن زورو، سأذهب لتفقده
Chouchou, this shop belongs to the two of us!
يا شوشو، هذا المحل ملكنا نحن الاثنان
This bag is too big for you, Chouchou!
هذا الكيس ثقيلٌ عليك يا شوشو
You don't want to get hurt, Chouchou!
ماذا سنفعل إن تأذيت يا شوشو؟
Just leave it to me!
اترك الأمر لي
Bad Chouchou! I told you not to eat the merchandise!
ألم أخبركَ ألا تأكل من بضاعة المحل يا شوشو؟
Now let's chow down!
هيا، لنأكل
Chouchou, I'm getting up there in years now.
يا شوشو، أمسيتُ طاعنًا بالسن
I gotta check in to the hospital.
سيتوجب عليّ المبيت في المشفى
But... I'm going to get better!
!ولكني سأتحسن حتمًا
Guard the shop well until I come back!
احمِ المحل جيِّدًا حتى عودتي
Hold down the fort!
!أعتمد عليك بحماية المكان
That tickles, Chouchou!
!هذا يدغدغ يا شوشو
I believe it's because Chouchou regards this shop as his treasure.
قد يكون ذلك لكون شوشو يعدّ هذا المحل كنزًا بالنسبة له
I think he continues to protect it in memory of his loving master.
وأعتقد أنه يستمر بحمايته لأنه يعده تذكارًا من صاحبه المحب للكلاب
Damn it! That dog even bit me!
!سحقًا! ذلك الكلب عضني حتى أنا
Wait! I just killed you!
!يفترض أني قتلتك قبل برهات يا هذا
It'll take more than that to kill me!
لن أموت بذلك القدر
Crush his head for sure this time!
!اقضم رأسه يقينًا هذه المرة
I won't lose to some lion!
!لن أهزم أمام أسدٍ سخيف
Gum-Gum...
فاكهة المطاط غومو غومو نو
Hammer!
المطرقة تشوتشي
Richie!
!ريتشي
Just what the hell are you?!
من أنت؟
I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit!
.أكلتُ فاكهة المطاط
Wait, you have devil fruit powers just like Captain Buggy?!
أيعقل أنك تتمتع بقدرة فاكهة شيطان كالقبطان باغي؟
It's too late for apologies...
لا داعي لأن تعتذر الآن
That dog's treasure is gone forever.
فإن كنز الكلب لن يرجع
That's why...
!ولهذا، سأُبرحك ضربًا
Pirates are all the same, every last one!
!جميع القراصنة يتشابهون
They take what people hold dear without a second thought!
يسلبون ما هو عزيزٌ على الأنفس بلا تردد ولا حساب للعواقب
So you survived, pirate!
أراكَ حيًّا أيها القرصان
I figured the lion would've eaten you for sure!
!اعتقدت تمامًا أن الأسد التهمك
As a pirate, you'll end up doing the same thing!
!أنت أيضًا ستفعل نفس الشيء كونك قرصان
You'll gather a crew and raid town after town!
عليّ قتلك ها هنا قبل أن تجمع طاقمًا وتهاجم الناس
Hey! Stop it, young lady!
!توقفي أيتها الشابة
As if you could ever kill me.
وكأنك تستطيعين قتلي
Let's test that theory!
!دعني أحاول إذًا
I said stop! What's with you people?!
أخبرتك أن تتوقفي! ما خطبكما؟
This is all I was able to get back.
لم أستطع استرجاع إلا هذا
That bastard went and ate the rest!
فقد التهم الباقي كله
He... fought with that lion.
...إنه... قاتل ذلك الأسد... من أجل الكلب
You fought good!
!قاتلت جيدًا
I didn't see you in action, but I can tell!
!لم أشاهدك، ولكن ذلك واضح
Yeah!
!أجل، ابذل جهدك أيضًا
You were beaten?!
!هُزمت؟
Mohji! I can't believe you'd lose to Zoro!
لم أظن أن زورو قد يطيح بك يا موجي
No, it wasn't Zoro! It was Straw Hat!
كلّا، لم يكن زورو، بل صاحب قبعة القش ذاك
What?! You got beat by the kid in the straw hat?!
!ماذا؟! طفل قبعة القش أطاح بك؟
He ate the... Gum...
-أكلَ... فاكـ
Now I'm pissed!
استشاط غضبي الآن
Ready all the Special Buggy Balls!
!جهزوا كل كرات باغي الخاصة التي بحوزتنا
I'm gonna blow this entire town to smithereens!
!سأبيد هذه البلدة على بكرة أبيها
Sorry for earlier!
أعتذر عمّا بدر مني
I didn't mean to yell at you...
...لم أقصد أن أفرغ غضبي عليك
It's okay! You've been through a lot!
لا بأس، فقد حدثت لك أمور كثيرة
I don't need the details, though.
لكني لا أريد سماعها
I'm so pathetic!
!يا لي من مثير للشفقة
If Chouchou and this youngster won't back down,
قاتل كلًّا من شوشو والصغير بشدَّة
then why am I, as mayor, content to watch the town get destroyed?!
فلمَ أجلس ساكنًا وأنا العمدة أشاهد بلدتنا تُدمّر؟
Calm down, Mayor!
!اهدأ أيها العمدة
Forty years ago, this place was nothing but barren land.
كانت هذه الأرض أرضًا قاحلةً قبل أربعين عامًا
We all worked together to clear and till the land,
تعاونّا جميعًا معًا لتصفية الأرض وحرث الحقول
open stores, and build our town.
وفتح المحلّات وإقامة بلدتنا
This town is a treasure to me and all its citizens!
!هذه البلدة كنزي وكنز جميع المواطنين
I won't let them have their way with it any longer!
!لن أسمح لهم باستبدادها أكثر من هذا
Fire a Special Buggy Ball! Blow the town away!
!أطلقوا كرة باغي الخاصة، أبيدوا البلدة
Even my own house...
...حتى منزلي
Zoro's sleeping in there!
!زورو ينام هناك
Hey! Zoro! Are you alive?!
أأنت حي يا زورو؟
That's a hell of a way to wake a guy up.
يا لها من طريقة فظيعة لإيقاظي من النوم
Not enough sleep...
...لم أنَم بما يكفي
And just how did you survive?!
كيف لكَ أن تكون حيًّا؟
Thank goodness! You're alive!
!ارتاح بالي، قد نجوت من ذلك
No more sitting idly by while they run wild here...
!لن أغفر لهم فعلتهم
I've had it up to here!
!لا أستطيع تحمل هذا أكثر
These scumbags have zero right to trample on these forty years!
!لا حق لحثالة يأتي فجأة ويدمر ما بنيناه خلال أربعين عامًا
I am this town's mayor!
!أنا عمدة هذه البلدة
I will protect this town!
!سأحمي هذه البلدة بنفسي
Stop! Stop, Mayor!
!تـ-تمهل أيها العمدة
No...! There are some fights a man can't run away from!
كلّا... هناك معارك لا ينبغي للرجال التهرب منها
Isn't that right, kiddo?!
!أليس كذلك أيها الصغير؟
That's right, old guy!
!صحيح أيها العجوز
Don't encourage him!
!لا تشجعه
What's he gonna change by facing them?! It's reckless!
ما الذي بإمكانه فعله بذهابه إليهم؟ لا طائل من هذا
It's absolutely reckless!
!أنا مدرك تمامًا أن هذا بلا طائل
I'm coming for you, Buggy the Clown!
!انتظرني يا باغي المهرج
The mayor was crying...
...العمدة... كان يبكي
He was? Not that I could see.
حقًّا؟ لم أرَ ذلك
Looks like the party's getting more exciting!
!يبدو أن الأمور زادت حماسة
You said it!
.هذا صحيح
This is no time to be laughing!
أهذا وقت الضحك؟
It's okay!
!لا بأس، يعجبني هذا العجوز
I'd never let him die!
!لن أدعه يموت مهما حدث
In that case...
...بما أنك قلت ذلك
You're going too?! But you're wounded!
!ستذهب أنت أيضًا بجرحك هذا؟
The injury to my name is much worse than the injury to my gut!
!جرح اسمي أسوأ بكثير من جرح معدتي
We're headed for the Grand Line.
.هدفنا هو الغراند لاين
So we're gonna swipe that map back from them!
!لذا سنسرق تلك الخريطة ثانيةً الآن
Join our crew, Nami!
رافقينا يا نامي
I won't become a pirate.
.لن أصبح قرصانةً
But how about this? We team up to achieve a common goal!
ماذا عن أن نتكاتف سعيًا نحو هدفنا المشترك؟
The second shot is ready, sir!
!الطلقة الثانية جاهزة
Alright! Fire!
!حسنًا، أطلِق
Get out here, Buggy the Clown!
!اخرج يا باغي المهرج
I am Mayor Boodle!
!أنا العمدة بودل
This town is our treasure, so I'm going to protect it by taking you out!
!أتيتُ من أجل حماية هذه البلدة، كنزنا. فلتواجهني
What are you, stupid?!
هل أنت غبي؟ الكنوز عبارة عن ذهب وفضة ومجوهرات
This town, a treasure?!
!البلدة كنز؟ كفاك سخافةً
You'd never understand how I feel–
يستحيل أن يفهم أمثالك شعوري
Soon, I'll conquer the Grand Line and flashily obtain all of the world's riches!
سأهيمن على الغراند لاين قريبًا وأحصل على كل ثروات العالم ببهرجة
It'll all belong to me!
!ثروات العالم ملك لي
No one else in this world needs treasure but me!
!لا داعي لأن يمتلك أحد الكنوز في هذا العالم غيري
Since you love this town so much, shall I level it along with you?
إن كانت هذه البلدة بهذه الأهمية بالنسبة لك، فما رأيك أن أمحيك معها؟
Quit blowing hot air and fight me!
!لا تثرثر وقاتلني
Don't get cocky now!
!لا تغتر بنفسك
The only way you'll destroy this town is over my dead body!
لن أسمح لك بتدمير هذه البلدة ولو كلفني ذلك حياتي
Fire!
!أطلِق
The straw hat guy!
!فتى قبعة القش
I'm here to kick your ass, just like I promised!
!أتيت لأبرح بك ضربًا كما وعدتك
How dare you just waltz back here...
!أيها الأوغاد... تجرؤون على القدوم ببجاحةٍ هكذا أمام القبطان باغي
Listen! All I want is the map and the treasure!
!أنصت، كل ما أريده هو الخريطة والكنز
Yeah, we know.
حسنًا، نعلم ذلك
Youngsters... Why'd you come here?!
أيها الصغار... لأيّ غايةٍ أتيتم؟
This isn't your business, so butt out!
!فليبقَ الغرباء خارج الموضوع
This is my fight!
!هذا قتالي، أنا سأحمي بلدتي
Now stop meddling!
!لا تتدخلوا
What the hell?!
!ماذا تفعل؟
Why did you attack the mayor?!
!لماذا هاجمت العمدة؟
He was in the way!
.إنه يعيقني
Good thinking.
.تفكير سليم
No doubt this geezer was prepared to die.
ينوي هذا العجوز الموت لو تركناه
This is for the best.
هذا أفضل
But this is going overboard!
!لا تتهور
There were plenty of other ways you could've done it!
!هناك عدّة طرق بإمكانك فعلها غير هذه
Hey, Big Nose!
!يا صاحب الأنف الكبير
That's the one thing you shouldn't say!
!هذا الشيء الوحيد الذي لا ينبغي لك قوله
How dare you...?
...كيف تجرؤ
Flashily fire the Buggy Ball!
!أطلقوا كرة باغي ببهرجة
Why'd you say that, you idiot?!
!لماذا قلت ذلك أيها الأحمق؟
Hey, Luffy! Run!
!اهرب يا لوفي
That...
...هذا
Time to blow up!
!فجّروه
...won't work on me!
!لن ينفع ضدي...
Gum-Gum...
فاكهة المطاط غومو غومو نو
Balloon!
البالون فوسين
What is that guy?!
ما خطبه؟
But the Buggy Ball will...
...لا يعقل أن كرة باغي سوف
He bounced it back!
!لقد ردّها
Give us a heads up first, will you?!
!أخبرنا بذلك مسبقًا
Alright! Took some out!
حسنٌ، انخفضت أعداد العدو
Seriously, what are you?!
ماذا تكون بجد؟
You had me there for a sec.
...لا تذعر الآخرين
Ever since fighting that lion, I knew you weren't quite normal!
عرفت أن هناك أمرًا غريبًا حين قاتلت ذلك الأسد
No human can do that! Explain yourself!
!هذه ليس حركات بشرية، فسّر هذا
What was that balloon-inflating thing you just did?!
ماذا كان الشيء المنفوخ كالبالون الذي فعلته توًّا؟
That's Gum-Gum Balloon!
.ذلك بالون المطاط
And how did you do that?!
!إني أسألك ما يكون هذا
What are you, a monster?!
هل أنت وحش؟
How dare you flashily try to do me in...
...كيف تجرؤ على الإطاحة بي ببهرجة
He used his henchmen as shields!
!استخدمَ أتباعه دروعًا
I couldn't eat another bite... H-Huh?
...لا يمكنني أكل المزيد
What happened here?!
!ماذا حدث هنا؟
You!
!أنت
Hey!
أهلًا
The straw hat guy!
!فتى قبعة القش
C-C-Captain Buggy! Be careful!
ا-ا-احذر أيها القبطان باغي
He has devil fruit powers too!
!إنه يتمتع بقدرة فاكهة شيطان
He's a rubber man!
!إنه رجل مطاطي
What?!
!ماذا؟
A rubber man?!
رجل مطاطي؟
Yeah, see?
أجل، انظري
A devil fruit, huh...?
...فاكهة شيطان إذًا
That explains how he bounced back the Buggy Ball.
هذا يفسر ردّه لكرة باغي
Our pirate crew has never been so insulted...
...هذه أعظم إهانة تلقاها طاقمنا في تاريخه
Captain.
أيها القبطان...
Oh, Cabaji! I'm so angry I'm seeing red.
كاباجي! أنا غاضب لدرجة أني لا أستطيع الضراط حتى
Cabaji! What the hell did you do to Richie?!
!أيها الوغد كاباجي! ما الذي فعلته بريتشي؟
This cat?
هذا القط؟
I used it to shield me so I wouldn't get my clothes dirty.
استخدمته كدرع لإبقاء ملابسي نظيفة
Richie!
!ريتشي
Hey, Richie! Say something! Are you all right?!
يا ريتشي، تماسك! هل أنت بخير؟
Dammit, you bastard!
!أيها الوغد اللعين
Out of the way!
!تنحّ عن طريقي
No, you get outta my way!
!بل أنت من عليه التنحي
I, First Officer Cabaji the Acrobat, will manifest Captain Buggy's displeasure!
أنا البهلواني كاباجي، الضابط الأول، سأحمل غضب القبطان باغي
I'll cross swords with you.
!إن كان الخصم سيَّافًا فأنا من سيواجهه
Quite the honor, Roronoa Zoro.
...يا له من شرف لي يا رورونوا زورو
As a swordsman myself, it will be my pleasure to cut you down.
لم أتوقع أن تسنح لي الفرصة بقطعك كوني سيافًا بدوري
Hey, Zoro! You should really rest!
!ارتح يا زورو، سأتولى أنا الأمر
Stay out of this!
!لا تتدخل
That's the stab wound the captain gave him. What a fool.
...هذا هو الجرح الذي أصابه القبطان به، أحمق
Acrobatics: Dire Fire!
التقنية البهلوانية: العجوز مفتعل الحرائق كيوغيكي: كاجي أوياجي
Something wrong?
ما الخطب؟
I'm sure I didn't kick you that hard.
لم أضربك بشدةٍ
He attacked his injury! He fights dirty!
!يا له من قذر، استهدف إصابته
Acrobatics: Steamy Hot Spring Murder Mystery!
التقنية البهلوانية: جريمة في حمّام البخار كيوغيكي: يوكيموري ساتسوجين جيكن
Acrobatics, my ass!
!ما البهلواني؟
That's just kicking up dust!
!إنها مجرد سحابة غبارية
He did it again!
!فعلها ثانيةً
What's wrong? A grown man wailing is disgraceful!
ما الخطب؟ من المخزي أن يئن رجل بالغ بهذا الشكل
Well? Now do you see how foolish it was...
هل أدركت الآن؟
to make an enemy of the Buggy Pirates?
أن اتخاذ قراصنة باغي عدوًا لكم كان حماقة؟
As hurt as he is, it's a miracle he's still alive!
!إنه جرح بليغ لدرجة أنه غريبٌ أن يكون حيًّا أصلًا
Why are you just standing there?! He's gonna get killed!
!لماذا تقف ساكنًا وتشاهده؟ سيُقتل
Roronoa Zoro...
...رورونوا زورو
You're finished!
!هُزم...
Annoying bastard!
!يا لك من وغد مزعج
Is poking my wound...
...هل وخز جرحي
that much fun?!
!ممتع إلى هذه الدرجة؟...
Ow!
!مؤلم
Wh-Why didn't you dodge that?!
لـ-لماذا لم تتفاداه؟
Is that enough of a handicap for you?
هل تكفيك هذه الأفضلية؟
Now I'll show you... just how outclassed you are!
!سأريك الآن الفجوة بين مستويَيْنا
So cool!
!مثير للإعجاب
So this is Roronoa Zoro, huh?
هذا هو رورونوا زورو إذًا؟
You think you can mock me...
...إنك تستخف بي
I won't stop until my swords rise to the top.
!تسعى سيوفي لتصبح الأعظم في العالم
I can't lose even once to anyone who's considered a swordsman!
!لا يسعني أن أخسر حتى مرة واحدة ضدّ من يدعو نفسه سيافًا
I see...
...هكذا إذًا
A strong resolve keeps you going.
عزيمة قوية تبقيك واقفًا على رجليك
But never fear.
.ولكن لا تقلق
Wounds as bad as yours will make an excellent excuse...
...جرح بليغ كهذا سيكون عذرًا أكثر من كافٍ
to explain why you lost to me!
!للخسارة ضدي...
To hell with that...
...لا تعبث معي
If I lose to someone like you when I'm barely even injured...
...إن خسرت ضد رجل مثلك بجرح خفيف كهذا
then my future isn't looking too bright!
!فلن يكون مستقبلي باهرًا...
Why, you...!
...أيها الوغد
You got this, Zoro!
!انطلق يا زورو
This is too much for me.
...لا أستطيع تحمّل هذا
You pirates go and get yourselves killed for all I care.
فلتتقاتلوا أنتم القراصنة وتؤذوا أنفسكم كما تشاؤون
Besides, I have no stake in whether you win or lose.
!لا يهمني من يفوز أو يخسر من بينكم
I'm gonna use this chance to swipe their treasure and get outta here!
سأنتهز هذه الفرصة لسلب الكنز ومغادرة هذا المكان
Let's team up again if we ever get the chance!
!لنتعاون إن ألقانا القدر معًا ثانية
See ya! Good luck with the fight!
!إلى اللقاء! أدعو لك بالحظ
Yeah! Thanks!
!أجل، شكرًا لك
Taste my ultimate acrobatic move!
!فلتذق حركتي البهلوانية المطلقة
Acrobatics: 100 Whirling Kamikaze Dervishes!
التقنية البهلوانية: رقصة مئة بلبل انتحاري كيوغيكي: كاميكازي هياكوما غيكيجو
Acrobatics...
التقنية البهلوانية: صعود الجبل كيوغيكي: ياما نوبورو
Acrobatics: Midsummer Fireworks!
التقنية البهلوانية: ألعاب نارية كيوغيكي: نوريو أوتشياغي هانابي
Whoa, he's flying!
!إنه مرتفع للغاية
Sting of the Unicycle!
لدغة الدراجة الأحادية إتشيرن زاشي
Ground-Hugging Chop-Chop Cannon!
مدفع التقطيع المقارب للأرض تشيو هاو بارا بارا هو
Cabaji! I'll hold Zoro down!
!كاباجي! أنا سأمسك زورو، أنهِ أمره
As you wish!
!مفهوم
You bastards!
!أيها الوغدان
Luffy!
!لوفي
Zoro's fight...
...قتال زورو
is off limits.
!لا تتدخل فيه...
I can defeat you easily enough without my captain's help!
بوسعي هزيمتك بسهولة حتى دون مساعدة قبطاني
Enough...
...يكفي... تعبت
Finally given up, have you?
ستستسلم أخيرًا إذًا؟
Though I must say, I'm impressed you could fight with such injuries.
بالأحرى، فوجئت أنك تمكنت من القتال بهذه الإصابات
Then I'll finish you off... with my...
...سأنهيك إذًا
real swordsmanship!
!بمهاراتي السيفية الحقيقية...
Die!
!مُت
Oni...
قاطع الشيطان أوني
Giri!
غيري
Cabaji!
!كاباجي
We, the Buggy Pirates...
...نحن، قراصنة باغي
beaten by mere thieves!
نُهزم علي يد لصوص متسللين...
"Thieves"? Nah...
لسنا لصوصًا متسللين
We're pirates!
!إننا قراصنة
Luffy! I'm gonna sleep now!
!سأنام الآن يا لوفي
Right!
!حسنًا، سأتكفل أنا بالباقي
You guys are pirates?!
!أنتما قراصنة؟
Yeah! We're headed for the Grand Line!
!أجل، وسنتوجّه للغراند لاين
Half-baked nobodies like you can't handle that kind of voyage, dimwit!
!إنها ليست رحلة بسيطة يمكن لغرّين مثلكما أن يتكفلا بها أيها الغبي
What are you gonna do in the Grand Line, anyway?!
ماذا ستفعلان بدخولكما إلى الغراند لاين على أي حال؟
Go on a sightseeing trip or something?
أتنويان السياحة أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
Become King of the Pirates!
.سأصبح ملك القراصنة
Get real, you flashy fool!
!لا تعبث معي أيها الغبي المتبهرج
If you're King of the Pirates, then I may as well be a god!
!أنت ملك القراصنة؟! أسيجعلني ذلك إلهًا إذًا؟
I'll be King of the Pirates and obtain all the world's treasures!
!أنا من سيصبح ملك القراصنة ويحصل على كنوز العالم كلها
Dream on!
!لا تحلم
You're annoying.
.إنك مزعج
Just bring it on already!
!تعال فحسب
That straw hat of yours reminds me of a certain man,
...رؤية قبعتك القشية تذكرني بذلك الرجل
and it really pisses me off!
!وذلك يغيظني للغاية
It reminds me...
!ذكريات أحمر الشعر اللعين المتغطرس ذاك
"Red-haired"?!
أحمر الشعر؟
You said "red-haired"!
أحمر الشعر... أيعقل أنك تعرف شانكس؟
Huh? Yeah, but what's it to you?
أجل، وما بذلك؟
Do you... know where he is?!
!أين هو الآن؟
Who can say?! I might know where he is,
،لا أعلم... ربّما أعرف أين هو
but, then again, maybe I don't!
!وقد أكون لا أعرف أين هو بتاتًا
That makes no sense.
ماذا تقول؟ أأنت أحمق؟
Look who's talking!
!أنتَ آخر من يتكلم
I'm not nice enough to tell you what you wanna know!
!لست لطيفًا لدرجة إخبارك بما تودّ معرفته ببساطة
Then I'll make you tell me!
!سأجبرك على ذلك بالقوة إذًا
I'll kill you before that ever happens!
!سأقتلك قبل أن يحدث ذلك
I doubt rubber can bounce back blades...
لا يمكن للمطاط أن يردّ النصل
Nope, it can't!
.نعم، ذلك مستحيل
Chop-Chop Slicecracker!
فاكهة التقطيع: بسكويت الأرز بارا بارا نو سنبن
Can't dodge in midair, can you?!
لا تستطيع التحرك في الهواء، أليس كذلك؟
Can too!
!أستطيع
Oh, my! Quite interesting!
!هكذا إذًا، مثير للاهتمام
Same to you!
!وأنت كذلك
Gum-Gum Pistol!
فاكهة المطاط غومو غومو نو
Your moves are interesting,
...إنها قدرة مثيرة للاهتمام
but they leave you wide open!
!ولكنك مليء بالثغرات الآن
Time to carve you up!
!سأقطعك
Gum-Gum...
فاكهة المطاط غومو غومو نو
Chop-Chop Quick Escape!
بارا بارا كنكيو داشتسو فاكهة التقطيع: الهروب السريع
Sickle!
كاما المنجل
Not good enough, "Gum-Gum"!
!ليس كافيًا أيها المطاطي
Damn, you keep coming apart!
!تبًّا، إنك تستمر بالتقطع
Wh-What a fight...
يـ-يا له من قتال... كأنني أعيش حُلمًا
Hey... Y-You see that?
أرأيت ذلك؟
You dumbass!
!أيها الأحمق، مثّل أنك مغمي عليك
Get caught up in that, and you'd never have enough lives to survive!
!إن تورطت بهذا، فحتى سبعة أرواحٍ لن تكيفك لتنجو
Chop-Chop Cannon!
بارا بارا هو مدفع التقطيع
Separate!
!انفصل
Well?! Do you see now, short stuff?!
أتعلمت الآن أيها الشقي؟
You bastard!
!أيها الوغد
Oh? Can't handle a little scratch to your face?
ما بالك؟ ألم ينبغي لي أن أجرح وجهك؟
How dare you...?
...كيف تجرؤ
How dare you damage this hat?!
!كيف تجرؤ على إضرار هذه القبعة؟
Huh?
نعم؟
This is my treasure!
!إنها كنزي
No one damages this hat and gets away with it!
!لن أغفر لأي أحد يضر بها
Yeah. I swore to the person who gave me this straw hat
...أجل، لقد أقسمت للرجل الذي منحني قبعة القش هذه
that I'd gather a crew and become a pirate!
!أني سأكوّن طاقمًا وأصبح قرصانًا
I thought there was nothing that could faze him...
...حسبت أن لا شيء يمكن أن يهزه
but he looks pretty upset.
...ولكن أن يستاء إلى هذه الدرجة
It would seem that hat has a history to it.
يبدو أن هذه القبعة عزيزة عليك جدًّا
That's right!
!هذا صحيح
Hmm? Is it that important of a hat?
أهي قبعة مهمة إلى هذه الدرجة؟
In that case...
...إذًا
take better care of it!
!احمِ ما هو عزيز عليك جيّدًا
I'll leave this hat with you.
سأترك هذه القبعة في عهدتك
It means a lot to me.
.إنها قبعتي العزيزة عليَّ
Take good care of it!
!اعتنِ بها جيّدًا
Come bring it back to me someday...
...عليكَ إعادتها لي يومًا
once you've become a great pirate!
!عندما تغدو قرصانًا عظيمًا...
That's our promise... Luffy!
!هذا وعد يا لوفي
You call this filthy straw hat a treasure?
أتقول إن هذه القبعة الرثَّة كنزك؟
Cut the crap!
!كُفّ عن الهراء
Shanks and I made a promise on that hat!
!هذه القبعة التي أقسمنا أنا وشانكس عليها
What?!
!ماذا؟
You're saying this is Shanks' hat?!
!أذلك يعني أنّ هذه قبعة شانكس؟
No wonder it seemed familiar!
!لا عجب أنها بدت مألوفة
He always wore this around me!
!لطالما ارتداها بجانبي
You and Shanks sailed aboard the same ship?!
أأبحرت رفقة شانكس على نفس السفينة؟
Yeah, back during our pirate apprenticeships.
أجل، حين كنا قرصانين متدربين
We were crewmates...
...كنّا رفيقين
me and that damn, detestable, red-haired bastard!
!ذلك المقيت اللعين أحمر الشعر
Shanks is a great man!
!شانكس رجل عظيم
You, his crewmate?!
!أتقول إنك رفيقه؟
Don't compare yourself to him!
!لا تجمع نفسك معه
Chop-Chop Quick Escape!
بارا بارا كنكيو داشتسو فاكهة التقطيع: الهروب السريع
Hi, I'm Buggy!
!إني باغي
Never say you and Shanks were crewmates ever again!
!لا تقل إنك رفيق شانكس ثانيةً
I can say whatever I want about Shanks!
!سأقول ما يحلو لي عن شانكس
Spill it!
أخبرني، ما الذي حدث بينك وبين شانكس؟
Damn!
تبًّا، كيف تجرؤ على فعل هذا بكنزي؟
Wanna know that badly?
أتريد المعرفة إلى هذه الدرجة؟
He's the one person...
...إنه الوحيد
I absolutely cannot forgive!
الذي لن أغفر له ما حييت...
I'll curse him for the rest of my life!
!سألعنه حتى آخر عمري
I'll never forgive him!
!إنه الوحيد الذي لن أغفر له ما حييت